(Howard:)One roll of toilet paper
and 20 minutes later,
(Howard:)I was so humiliated,
(Howard:)I snuck out the window
and never saw her again.
(Emily:)You know what else
(Emily:)my security deposit.
(Howard:)I'm sorry.
(Howard:)I tried to unclog it,
but you didn't have a plunger,
(Howard:)and water was
spilling out everywhere.
(Emily:)Right, just water.
(Howard:)Look, I have felt terrible
about this for years,
(Howard:)and I'm glad I have the opportunity
to tell you just how sorry I am.
(Emily:)It's fine.
(Emily:)All my friends love this story.
(Emily:)They call you Clogzilla.
(Raj:)Get it? Because you
clogged up her bathroom
(Raj:)like a radioactive monster!
(Howard:)-Yeah, yeah, I get it.
-Howie.
(Howard:)Well, hey, it's not like
cotton candy comes out of you.
(Amy:)Come on, let's get you to bed.
You've had a lot to drink.
(Sheldon:)No more than Penny.
(Amy:)That's what I'm saying.
(Sheldon:)Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait...